{
    "event_data": {
        "event_id": 1,
        "game_id": 1,
        "game_title": "20220606 - A - Sound",
        "join_code": "1234",
        "block_code": "20220606 - A - Sound",
        "current_round_number": 1,
        "current_question_number": 1
    },
    "game_rounds": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "title": "General Knowledge",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "title": "Stay Cool",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "title": "Where Do You Pronounce It Like That?",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "title": "Alphabetical Initials",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 4
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "title": "The Rainbow Flag",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 5
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "title": "It\u2019s Independence Day Somewhere",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 6
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "title": "General Knowledge",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 7
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "title": "Retro Vibes",
            "round_description": "",
            "round_number": 8
        }
    ],
    "game_questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What band\u2014none of whose members were actually related to one another\u2014first hit the Billboard Top 100 in 1977 with the song \u201cSheena is a Punk Rocker\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "The Ramones",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 1,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "1.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "If you've spent the day driving around Peach Beach, Banshee Boardwalk, and Rainbow Road, you're playing an installment of what video game franchise?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "\u201cMario Kart\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 1,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "1.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "\u201cSelenology\u201d is defined as the scientific study of the\u2026 what?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Moon",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 1,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "1.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "Which Caribbean nation has a name that translates to English as \u201cthe bearded ones?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Barbados",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 1,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "1.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What term for a day of special significance dates back to the days of the Roman Republic, when a certain color ink was used to mark these days on the calendar?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Red Letter Day",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 1,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "1.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "Jimmy Cliff\u2019s cover of the song \u201cI Can See Clearly Now\u201d hit the charts in 1993 after it was used in what movie\u2014a wildly fictionalized retelling of the 1988 Winter Olympics in Calgary?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "\u201cCool Runnings\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 2,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "2.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "What \u201890s rapper, who has desperately been trying to keep his trademark braids despite going bald in recent years, performed the theme song for the TV show \u201cKenan and Kel\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Coolio",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 2,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "2.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "What character actor, who also appeared in \u201cAmerican Pie,\u201d is so recognizable for her role in \u201cLegally Blonde\u201d that she reprised it in 2018 for Ariana Grande\u2019s \u201cthank u, next\u201d video?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Jennifer Coolidge",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 2,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "2.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "What snack food, originally available only in \u201cToasted Corn\u201d flavor, sells one of its most popular flavors in much of Europe under the branding \u201cCool American\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Doritos",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 2,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "2.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cWhat we\u2019ve got here is failure to communicate\u201d is No. 11 on the American Film Institute\u2019s list of the \u201c100 Greatest Movie Quotes of All Time.\u201d It\u2019s a line from what movie?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "\u201cCool Hand Luke\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 2,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "2.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "A city on the French Riviera, or pretty cool.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Nice",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 3,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "3.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "A fancy street in Beverly Hills, or a showcase for cowboys and cowgirls.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Rodeo",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 3,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "3.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "The capital of Peru, or another name for a butter bean.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Lima",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 3,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "3.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "A city in Texas, or a street in New York.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Houston",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 3,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "3.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "A mountain in Washington, or what the Pacific Northwest is, compared to the Southwest.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Rainier",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 3,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "3.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Antonio Banderas",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "4.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Clea DuVall",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "4.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Ella Fitzgerald",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "4.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "George Harrison",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "4.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this character.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Indiana Jones",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "4.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Kellan Lutz",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 6,
            "key": "4.6"
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Martina Navratilova",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 7,
            "key": "4.7"
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this character.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Olivia Pope",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 8,
            "key": "4.8"
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this thing.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Queen\u2019s Rook",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 9,
            "key": "4.9"
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "question_type": "Image Round",
            "question_text": "Name this person.",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Shirley Temple",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 4,
            "question_number": 10,
            "key": "4.10"
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "Designer Gilbert Baker created the Pride flag in 1978. Its rainbow originally included the color pink, but it was eventually dropped due to pink fabric being more expensive than the other colors. How many stripes are now in the standard Pride flag?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "6",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 5,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "5.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "The \u201cProgress Pride Flag,\u201d designed by Daniel Quasar in 2018, adds black, brown, light blue, light pink, and white to the classic rainbow flag in what shape?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Triangle",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 5,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "5.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "The White House was illuminated in rainbow flag colors following the Supreme Court ruling on Obergefell v. Hodges in 2015. What was the impact of that decision?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Legalized gay marriage",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 5,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "5.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "Lena Waithe made a splash in 2018 when she wore a cope\u2014that\u2019s a liturgical cape worn by a Catholic bishop\u2014made out of a rainbow flag to what annual event, whose theme that year was \u201cFashion and the Catholic Imagination\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "The Met Gala",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 5,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "5.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question_type": "Themed Round",
            "question_text": "A large Pride flag flies year-round at the corner of Market and Castro streets in San Francisco, over a plaza named after what politician?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Harvey Milk",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 5,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "5.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "question_type": "Lightning Round",
            "question_text": "June 30, 1960: Democratic Republic of the Congo",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Belgium",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 6,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "6.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "question_type": "Lightning Round",
            "question_text": "January 1, 1804: Haiti",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "France",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 6,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "6.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "question_type": "Lightning Round",
            "question_text": "December 6, 1917: Finland",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Russia",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 6,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "6.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "question_type": "Lightning Round",
            "question_text": "July 28, 1821: Peru",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Spain",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 6,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "6.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "question_type": "Lightning Round",
            "question_text": "August 15, 1947: India",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "United Kingdom",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 6,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "6.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What classic American game show, often parodied on \u201cRuPaul\u2019s Drag Race,\u201d was replicated in the U.K. and Australia under the name \u201cBlankety Blanks\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "\u201cMatch Game\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 7,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "7.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What vehicle brand takes its name from the Italian word for \u201cwasp\u201d?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Vespa",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 7,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "7.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What Germanic tribe sacked Rome in 455, and had a name that lives on today as a word that describes people who participate in the destruction of property?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Vandals",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 7,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "7.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "Brass is an alloy of copper and zinc. Bronze is an alloy of copper and\u2026 what?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Tin",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 7,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "7.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question_type": "General Knowledge",
            "question_text": "What theatrical performance, which has been seen live by more than 25 million people worldwide, began in 1994 as a 7-minute interlude during the Eurovision Song Contest that told the history of Irish immigration to America?",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "\u201cRiverdance\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 7,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "7.5"
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "question_type": "Sound Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cThere were nights of endless pleasure / \nIt was more than all your laws allow / \nBaby, baby, baby / \nWhen you touch me like this / \nAnd when you hold me like that\u201d",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Celine Dion, \u201cIt\u2019s All Coming Back to Me Now\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 8,
            "question_number": 1,
            "key": "8.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "question_type": "Sound Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cIf I only could / \nI'd make a deal with God / \nAnd I'd get him to swap our places / \nBe running up that road\u201d",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Kate Bush, \u201cRunning Up That Hill\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 8,
            "question_number": 2,
            "key": "8.2"
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "question_type": "Sound Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cWe were as one, babe / \nFor a moment in time / \nAnd it seemed everlasting / \nThat you would always be mi\u2013\u201d",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Mariah Carey, \u201cAlways Be My Baby\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 8,
            "question_number": 3,
            "key": "8.3"
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "question_type": "Sound Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cLast night, I was taking a walk along the river / \nAnd I saw him together with a young girl / \nAnd the look that he gave her made me shiver / \n'Cause he always used to look at me that way\u201d",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "ABBA, \u201cAngeleyes\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 8,
            "question_number": 4,
            "key": "8.4"
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "question_type": "Sound Round",
            "question_text": "\u201cI'm not a perfect person / \nThere's many things I wish I\u2013\u201d",
            "question_url": "",
            "display_answer": "Hoobastank, \u201cThe Reason\u201d",
            "answer_notes": "",
            "round_number": 8,
            "question_number": 5,
            "key": "8.5"
        }
    ],
    "round_states": [
        {
            "round_number": 1,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 2,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 3,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 4,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 5,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 6,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 7,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        },
        {
            "round_number": 8,
            "locked": false,
            "scored": false
        }
    ],
    "question_states": [
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 1,
            "key": "1.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 1,
            "key": "1.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 1,
            "key": "1.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 1,
            "key": "1.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 1,
            "key": "1.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 2,
            "key": "2.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 2,
            "key": "2.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 2,
            "key": "2.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 2,
            "key": "2.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 2,
            "key": "2.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 3,
            "key": "3.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 3,
            "key": "3.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 3,
            "key": "3.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 3,
            "key": "3.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 3,
            "key": "3.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.6",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.7",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.8",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.9",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "round_number": 4,
            "key": "4.10",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 5,
            "key": "5.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 5,
            "key": "5.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 5,
            "key": "5.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 5,
            "key": "5.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 5,
            "key": "5.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 6,
            "key": "6.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 6,
            "key": "6.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 6,
            "key": "6.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 6,
            "key": "6.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 6,
            "key": "6.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 7,
            "key": "7.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 7,
            "key": "7.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 7,
            "key": "7.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 7,
            "key": "7.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 7,
            "key": "7.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "round_number": 8,
            "key": "8.1",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "round_number": 8,
            "key": "8.2",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "round_number": 8,
            "key": "8.3",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "round_number": 8,
            "key": "8.4",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "round_number": 8,
            "key": "8.5",
            "question_displayed": false,
            "answer_displayed": false
        }
    ]
}
